教练:出手,抓住那些葡萄,给这家伙右脸上来一拳.
Coach: And reach and stretch and grab those grapes, and punch that guy right in the face.
开萝尔:全优生不应该不得不学健身.
Carol: Grade A students shouldn't have to take gym.
德比:哦,说得对,开萝尔.大家真的应该追求头脑的曲线.
Debbie: Oh, yeah Carol. Guys really go for a curvy brain.
雪莉:如果不是为了大腿曲线,谁来这儿啊?
Shelly: If it weren't for my shapely thighs, where would I be?
开萝尔:哪个真正成功的女人会担心大腿的曲线呢?
Carol: Name just one serious successful woman who worries about the shape of her thighs?
雪莉:爱瓦娜·怀特.
Shelly: Evana White.
开萝尔:哦,为什么,我怎么没有想到她?
Carol: Oh why, oh why didn't I think of her?
校长:请大家注意,我是你们的校长,德维特先生.
Principle: Attention people, this is your principle, Mr. Dewitt speaking.
众女生:喔!
Girls: Wooooh!
校长:看着我的脸,早上好,同学们.是的,就是我.我通过德维中学全新的录像系统和你们见面.你们的父母们都在工作.
Principle: Point it at my face. There we go. Good morning, students. Yes, it's me. Coming to your via the all new Dewey High school Pa system Hooter vision. Your parents tax dollars at work.
开萝尔:看起来像是1984年.
Carol: This is like something out of Nineteen Eighty Four.
校长:离返校节舞会只剩下两天了,筹委会仍需要帮助.如果你们还能提供以下一些装饰品,比如气球,腰带,鞋子,洋娃娃,鞭子,手铐,哦,手铐还是算了,你们请联系布奇?尼豪瑟. 我很想马上在我的办公室看到布奇?尼豪瑟.现在,一个重要新闻,宣布你们选出的返校节国王和王后候选人.
Principle: The homecoming dance is only two days away, and the decorating committee still needs help. Contact Bucky Kneehowser if you can donate any of the following decorative items; balloons, streamers, slap shoes, chaps, whips, handcuffs... ok forget this item. And I'd like to see Bucky Kneehowser in my office PDQ. And now the big news. The candidates who you have selected for homecoming king and queen.
众女生:喔!
Girls: Woooo!
校长:我也很激动.埃斯特尔,把信封递给我.
Principle: I get tingles too. Estelle, the envelope, please.
德比:就像是颁发学校奖学金.
Debbie: It's just like the Academy awards.
开萝尔:哦,罗勃?罗维,罗勃?罗维是会被提名,还是再次等到下一年?
Carol: Oh yeah, will Rob Lowe be nominated, or passed over for yet another year?
雪莉:肯定是后者.
Shelly: Exactly.
开萝尔:看你们这些人,好像这很重要似的.
Carol: Can you guys hear yourselves, you act like this is important.
德比:哦,我想你无所谓?
Debbie: Oh and I suppose you're above all this?
开萝尔:这只不过是社交礼仪的陈述而已,自从幼儿园以来就一直灌输的流行文化.
Carol: This is merely an affirmation of a social order, which has been instilled on our popular culture since kindergarten.
雪莉:我想德比不懂你所说的.
Shelly: I don't think Debbie understands what you mean.
开萝尔:每年提名的都是相同的几个.我以为这些人对学校的最大贡献就是长得还可以.
Carol: Every year, it's the same chosen few that get nominated. The in crowd, the A list, the sociees. And I'm talking about people whose biggest contribution to this school is looking good in a sweater.
校长:如果你们在教师休息室里花点时间,吃些油炸圈饼,也许你们就会发现……好了,算了,候选人放学后在礼堂集中,做一些简要说明.首先按字母顺序宣布王后候选人,约雅?巴奈斯.
Principle: Maybe if you spent less time in the teacher's lounge stuffing your face with doughnuts, you'd find it... Okee Dokee. Candidates meet in the auditorium after school for briefing. First the candidates for Queen, in alphabetical order: Joya Barnes.
开萝尔:那个穿紧身衣,却总是忘记带胸罩的女生叫什么名字?
Carol: And who's the girl in the tight sweater who always forgets to wear a bra?
校长:詹尼弗?卡勒斯提诺.
Principle: Jennifer Calestino.
开萝尔:就是她.我们还得找一个或者两个拉拉队长.
Carol: That's her. And we must have a cheerleader or two.
校长:苏扎娜?弗里曼.
Principle: Suzanne Fryman.
开萝尔:一个.
Carol: One.
校长:何瑟?马克姆贝.
Principle: Heather Macombe.
开萝尔:两个.
Carol: Two.
德比:你们是在说只有最受欢迎的人才能获提名吗?
Debbie: So you are saying that only the most popular kids get nominated?
开萝尔:的确如此.
Carol: Exactly.
校长:开萝尔?西维尔.
Principle: And Carol Seaver.
开萝尔:另一个.什么?
Carol: Another case and point. What?
雪莉:我敢打赌,你后悔锻炼你的大腿了吧.
Shelly: I'll bet you are sorry now you let your thighs go to hell.
德比:我从来就没和那些人成为最好的朋友,
Debbie: I've never been best friends with someone in the in crowd before.
开萝尔:我也不是.
Carol: I'm not in the in crowd.
德比:我们拍完照后,马上去查德维克,给你挑一件衣服.
Debbie: As soon as we've finished having this picture taken, we are going to go to Chadwick's and we're going to pick you out a dress.
雪莉:小狗才去查德维克购物呢.
Shelly: Only dogs shop at Chadwick's.
德比:我在查德维克购物.
Debbie: I shop at Chadwick's.
雪莉:可事实上,它们连一件稍微露点胸的衣服都没有.
Shelly: Exactly. They don't have a single dress there that shows any bosom.
德比:这有问题吗?
Debbie: What does that matter?
雪莉:对于你当然没什么.但是开萝尔想成为王后,当你们投票时,露点胸大有好处.
Shelly: For you, not much. But Carol wants to be queen, and when you're going for votes, a little bosom goes a long way.
(梦境)
(dream scene)
校长:我们少了一个候选人,那个女生在哪?
Principle: We are missing a candidate. Where's the other girl?
开萝尔:在这儿,德维特先生.
Carol: Right here Mr. Dewitt.
校长:你?哈哈哈.你不可能是王后候选人.你一点胸也没露,开萝尔?西维尔.
Principle: You? Ha ha ha. You can't be a queen candidate. You're not showing any bosom. Carol Seaver.
开萝尔:不,我不露胸.
Carol: No, no bosom.
校长:好吧.那加入我们吧.西维尔小姐.现在请记住,同学们都在看着你,因此不要四处乱瞅,也不要作出下流手势.
Principle: Ok. Care to join us Miss Seaver. Now remember people, that the student body looks up to you. So no crossed eyes, or obscene gestures.
开萝尔:(暗想)我在返校节的台上.我,有头脑的开萝尔?西维尔,我还怎么有脸见我的爸爸妈妈呢?
Carol: (in her head) I'm in the homecoming court. Me, Carol-the brain-Seaver. How am I ever going to face mum and dad?
(梦境)
(dream scene)
开萝尔:你好.
Carol: Hi
杰森:宝贝,我们最优秀,最聪明的孩子回家了.
Jason: Honey, the best and brightest of our children is home.
麦琪:你说的是那个全优生,象棋俱乐部的成员,美国未来的物理学家,我生活的支柱的女儿.是她吗?
Maggie: You mean the one who gets a consistent four point 0 average, is a member of the chess club, the future physicists of America and is the daughter I vicariously live my life through. That child?
杰森:就是她.
Jason: That's the one.
麦琪:好的,我得把我正在写的稿子放一边.
Maggie: Well let me just put this darn freelance article I'm writing aside.
杰森:我也待会饲养我的鸭子.
Jason: I can stuff my duck anytime.
麦琪:开萝尔,告诉我们你今天又在学校取得了哪些惊人的成绩?
Maggie: Carol, tell us what startling achievements you made at school today?
开萝尔:妈妈,爸爸,我有一些消息,可能会让你们目瞪口呆.
Carol: Mum, dad, I have some news that might be dramatic for you.
杰森:小姑娘,如果你赢得了诺贝尔奖,而没有告诉我们,我们可得好好的惩罚你.
Jason: Young lady, if you've gone and won the Nobel prize and didn't call us, you're in big trouble.
开萝尔:我可没有.
Carol: No, I didn't.
杰森:好的,谁管它呢.无论怎么样,你都是我们的快乐.
Jason: Ah, who cares. You are a joy to parent anyway.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
麦琪:你关心兄妹.
Maggie: A devoted sibling.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
杰森:你热爱祖国.
Jason: A credit to this nation.
开萝尔:爸爸,你真是一个马屁精.
Carol: Dad, you're being a sycophant.
杰森:谢谢你.
Jason: Thank you.
麦琪:开萝尔,你能告诉我什么是马屁精吗?
Maggie: Carol, would you please tell me what a sycophant is.
开萝尔:以后吧,妈妈.看,我今天被提名为返校节王后了.
Carol: Later mum. See, today I was nominated for home coming queen.
杰森和麦琪:(哭泣)
Jason and Maggie: (crying)
迈克:这儿好多的烟.
Mike: Boy it's foggy in here.
麦琪:迈克,现在你是我们最大的希望.
Maggie: Mike, you're our best hope now.
杰森:答应我们你可不要成为返校节王后.
Jason: Promise us you'll never become home coming queen.
迈克:爸爸,这是一个电炉.这儿发生什么事了?
Mike: Dad, it's an electric oven. What the heck is going on around here?
开萝尔:我已经被提名为返校节女王了.
Carol: I've been nominated for homecoming queen.
迈克:嘿,那真厉害.今年是要办成马戏团吗?
Mike: Hey, that's tough. So is it like a circus theme this year?
本:奶酪,奶酪,奶酪.我需要奶酪来对付我的排骨.嘿,你们这些人没听见我要什么吗?
Ben: Cheese, cheese, cheese. I need cheese to go with my rack of ribs. Hey didn't any of you people hear what I need?
返校节女生:奶酪!
Homecoming girls: Cheese!
摄影师:那个女生没有笑.
Photographer: That girl didn't smile.
校长:西维尔小姐,你能笑一下吗?
Principle: Miss Seaver, could you be happy for just a moment?
开萝尔:怎么了?
Carol: How's that?
校长:很好.
Principle: Fine.
杰森:好的,克莉丝.我给你买了尿布,卫生纸,洗手液,奶瓶,拨浪鼓,盐,胡椒……哦,你不需要这些.你还需要什么呢?
Jason: Ok Chris. I got your diapers, your wipes, your lotion, your bottle, your rattle, your salt, your pepper...nah! You don't need those do you? Anything else you need?
迈克:爸爸,我能借些钱吗?
Mike: Dad, can I borrow some money?
杰森:什么.迈克,不行.
Jason: Pardon. Mike, no.
迈克:哦,爸爸,不过才二十块,星期五还你.我的意思是,如果你需要帮忙的话,尽管说.
Mike: Oh come on dad. Just twenty bucks till Friday. I mean if you ever need a favour, you got it.
杰森:只要二十?
Jason: Only twenty?
迈克:实际上……
Mike: Well actually...
杰森:你最多只能得到二十.
Jason: Twenty is all you're getting.
迈克:好吧.你这个小气鬼,爸爸.
Mike: Alright, you drive a hard bargain dad.
麦琪:杰森,我们得赶快.如果去儿科医生那晚了五分钟,他会让我们等一小时.你知道医生什么都做得出来?
Maggie: Jason we have to hurry. If we are five minutes late for this pediatrician, he'll make us wait an hour. You know how impossible doctors can be?
杰森:是的,我听见了.
Jason: Yeah, I've heard.
麦琪:哦,杰森,克瑞斯要换尿布了.
Maggie: Oh Jason, Chrissy has to be changed.
杰森:迈克,帮个忙.
Jason: Mike. Favour time.
迈克:哦,爸爸!好吧.我们去照看克莉丝吧.
Mike: Oh dad! Alright. Let's get this over with Chrissy.
开萝尔:你好.
Carol: Hi.
麦琪:宝贝,你好.学校怎么样?
Maggie: Hi honey. How was school?
开萝尔:很顺利.妈妈,爸爸,我可以和你们两个谈一谈吗?
Carol: Well I might as well get this over with. Mum, dad, can I talk to the two of you.
麦琪:当然可以,宝贝.
Maggie: Well of course sweet heart.
开萝尔:也许你们最好坐下.
Carol: Maybe you better sit.
杰森:开萝尔,有这么严肃吗?
Jason: Carol, is this serious?
开萝尔:我想是这样.现在我知道你们都认为我是个聪明的孩子,你们一个可以出人头地的孩子.不,不是这样.你们可以想象我今天听到我被提名为返校节王后时什么感觉.
Carol: I'm afraid so. Now I know that both have always thought of me as the sensible one. Your one child with her head on the ground and feet out of the clouds. No that's wrong. Anyway, you can well imagine how I felt today when, when I found out that, that I was nominated for home coming queen.
杰森:那很神圣,那是
Jason: Holy cow, that is...
麦琪:开萝尔,那太棒了.
Maggie: Carol, that is wonderful.
开萝尔:恭喜!爸爸,我被推选为拉拉队长.
Carol: Congratulations! Dad, I'm being lumped in with cheerleader.
杰森:喔.我的一些好朋友也是拉拉队长.
Jason: Uh hu. Well some of my favorite people are cheerleaders.
开萝尔:但是其余的候选人只是漂亮和受欢迎.
Carol: But all the other nominees are just pretty and popular.
麦琪:宝贝,那有什么关系呢?
Maggie: Well honey, what's wrong with that?
开萝尔:有关系.妈妈,返校节上的人都是没什么出息的.你认为特瑞莎修女当过返校节王后吗?
Carol: Wrong. Mum, people in the homecoming court are never people of consequence. Do you think mother Theresa was a homecoming queen?
杰森:哦,你知道她没有当过?
Jason: Oh, you know for a fact that she wasn't?
开萝尔:好,好.我们拿妈妈做例子吧.她从来不会陷入这种愚蠢的事情.
Carol: Alright, alright. So we'll take mum for example. She'd never be part of something silly like this.
麦琪:实际上我当过返校节王后.
Maggie: Well actually I was homecoming queen.
开萝尔:这解释太轻率了.
Carol: That explains so much.
麦琪:开萝尔,你可以成为一个有出息的人,而且还又受欢迎,又漂亮.
Maggie: Carol you can be a person of substance and still be popular and pretty.
开萝尔:你不谈谈爱瓦娜·怀特呢?
Carol: You're not talking about Evana White, are you?
杰森:你说得对.
Jason: There you go.
开萝尔:你们不能明白,那些投票提名我的人不了解我是个什么样的人.
Carol: Can't you see. The people who voted to nominate me don't know who or what I am.
杰森:那又如何?
Jason: And what's that?
开萝尔:我自己的父亲都不了解我是一个什么样的人.
Carol: My own father doesn't know what I am.
杰森:你了解你自己吗?
Jason: Well do you know what you are?
麦琪:哦,杰森,告诉她,她是什么样的.
Maggie: Oh Jason, just tell her what she is.
迈克:我很乐意做这些.你说的对,爸爸.相信我,我会挣这二十块钱的.
Mike: I'd be happy to do it. There you go dad. Believe me, I earned that twenty bucks. And some change.
麦琪:开萝尔宝贝,这是个好消息.你不必为此难过.
Maggie: Carol honey, this is wonderful news. There is nothing here for you to get upset about.
迈克:什么消息?
Mike: What news?
杰森:别打听,迈克.
Jason: Not now Mike.
开萝尔:不,不,没问题.我想听听迈克说什么.迈克,我已经被提名为返校节的王后了.
Carol: No, no. It's alright. I'd like to hear what Mike has to say. Mike, I've been nominated for home coming queen.
迈克:这是一个玩笑吗?
Mike: What this is some kind of joke, right?
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
迈克:听起来今年是一个马戏团的主题了?
Mike: So like is it a circus theme this year?
开萝尔:谢谢,迈克.傻瓜总是说真话.
Carol: Thank you. Mike. A lonely fool speaks the truth.
(开萝尔的梦境)
(Carol's dream)
女孩:谢谢你,德维特先生,谢谢你,我的家人,我的朋友和那些渴望成为我的朋友的人.感谢你们每一个盯着我性感胸脯的人.没有你们,我不会成为这样的女孩.
Girl: Thank you Mr. Dewitt. Thank you my family, my friends and those of you who dream of being my friends. Thank you everyone who clings unto my prize bosom. I couldn't be the regular gal I am without you.
校长:说得很好,不过很空洞.最后一名,最差的开萝尔·西维尔.
Principle: What a lovely, all be it empty, sentiment. Last and certainly least, Carol Seaver.
开萝尔:胸够了吗,雪莉?
Carol: Enough bosom for you Shelly?
雪莉:很好,也足够了.
Shelly: Good and plenty.
德比:真美,真美,真美.
Debbie: Lovely, lovely, lovely.
校长:开萝尔?西维尔,我们在等你呢.
Principle: Carol Seaver, we're waiting.
开萝尔:我看起来怎么样?哦,不!你认为你和他们一样吗?哈!
Carol: How do I look? Oh no. You! You think you are in the same league as these people? Ha!
校长:现在西维尔,出来!不!
Principle: Now Seaver. Move it! Don't!
所有人:(大笑)
Everyone: (laughing)
迈克:先生们,女士们,如果你们注意到场地中央,你们会看见我们伟大的纽约城中最胖的女人,别害怕,她只是在经历这样一个阶段.
Mike: Ladies and gentlemen. If you will direct your attention to the centre ring, and feast your eyes on the largest woman in the great state of New York. Don't be alarmed. She is merely going through a stage.
(闹铃声)
(alarm clock)
开萝尔:我永远也不要那样.
Carol: That's one stage I'm never going through.
迈克:嘿!早上好,爸爸.
Mike: Hey! Morning, dad.
杰森:你好,迈克.你今天起得真早.
Jason: Hi mike. You're up bright and early this morning.
迈克:嗯,你做火腿和鸡蛋的声音吵醒了我.
Mike: Yeah, well the noise of you cooking bacon and eggs woke me.
杰森:下次我一定多注意一些.
Jason: I'll try to be more careful next time.
迈克:给你说实话吧,爸爸,我早就起来学习了,当我想吃早餐时,我发现没饼干了.
Mike: You know, to tell you the truth dad, I was up early to study, and well I was going to make breakfast but I ran out of crackers.
杰森:迈克,你想吃早餐?迈克!
Jason: Mike, you want some breakfast? Mike!
迈克:哦,喔.我从来也不会请求你们,早上好,妈妈.
Mike: Oh wow. You know it never occurred to me to impose on you guys. Morning, mum.
麦琪:早上好.
Maggie: Morning.
迈克:你们给我做了这么多好吃的.
Mike: You guys are great feeding me like this.
麦琪:放下你的叉子,那是开萝尔的.
Maggie: Put down your fork, this is Carol's.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
杰森:我不知道你会来和我们一起吃早餐,迈克,所以我没有给你煮鸡蛋.但是有很多的麦片.
Jason: Well I didn't know you'd be joining us for breakfast Mike, so I didn't cook you any eggs. But there is plenty of cereal.
迈克:麦片,你们就请我在这儿吃麦片?
Mike: Cereal, you guys invited me in here for cereal?
杰森:你要愿意,饼干也可以.
Jason: Well crackers if you prefer.
本:嘿,迈克,你想要火腿上的肥肉吗?
Ben: Hey Mike, you want the shiny part of my bacon?
杰森:开萝尔没下来?
Jason: Carol's not down yet?
麦琪:没有,她还是想不通.
Maggie: No. She's still not herself.
本:我真高兴开萝尔会有麻烦.
Ben: I love it when Carol's in the dumper.
开萝尔:早上好,妈妈,爸爸,本和迈克尔.
Carol: Good morning mum, dad, Ben and Michael.
麦琪:宝贝,你好吗?
Maggie: Honey, how are you?
开萝尔:我感觉像是坐在世界之巅.
Carol: I'm sitting on top of the world.
迈克:那是冰岛.
Mike: Look out Iceland.
杰森:够了,迈克.
Jason: Enough Mike.
开萝尔:没关系,那很有趣.
Carol: No, that was funny.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
开萝尔:迈克说的?那真有趣.
Carol: What Mike said? It was funny.
迈克:那是一个蹩脚的笑话.
Mike: It was a fat joke.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
本:这里究竟怎么回事?
Ben: What the heck's going on here?
麦琪:迈克的玩笑通常并不有趣.
Maggie: Usually you find Mikes jokes anything but funny.
本:不有趣,只是有点刺激,妈妈.
Ben: But funny. That's a hot one mum.
开萝尔:昨晚我做了一个很神奇的梦.我冷静,我沉着,我的行程安排好了.我清楚地知道自己要做什么,如何去做.我的所有能量都为了这一个目标,我没有什么好分心的,当然我也不会去玩这种愚蠢幼稚的游戏.
Carol: Well last night I had an insightful vision. I'm cool, I'm calm, and my course is set. I know exactly what I have to do and how I'm going to do it. All my energy is directed into one purpose, and I have none to spare for distractions. And certainly not the primal ramblings of this pimple faced pus bag.
迈克:那很好.
Mike: That's better.
雪莉:开萝尔,你去哪了?你只有五分钟来让自己打扮得漂亮一些.赶快!
Shelly: Carol, where have you been? You only have five minutes to make yourself presentable. Go!
开萝尔:我在和苏黎世先生讨论罗马帝国的衰落.
Carol: I was talking to Mr. Zurich about the fall of the Roman Empire.
德比:罗马帝国的衰落?我们这里有一次选举,你却在考虑凯撒.
Debbie: Fall of the Roman Empire? We've got an election here, and you are thinking about Caesar.
开萝尔:关于返校节的事情,我想了很多.
Carol: I thought a lot about this home coming stuff.
雪莉:我带了我所有的化妆品.
Shelly: I brought all my shades.
德比:雪莉,这让开萝尔看起来像一个流浪汉.
Debbie: Shelly, making Carol look like a tramp, is not the way to go about this.
开萝尔:我已经决定了
Carol: And I've decided...
雪莉:流浪汉!
Shelly: Tramp!
开萝尔:在考虑很久以后.
Carol: After much rational thought.
德比:这儿,用我的粉底.
Debbie: Here. Use my blusher.
开萝尔:以及一个非常有象征意义的梦.
Carol: And a highly symbolic dream.
雪莉:这是你马上要穿的?
Shelly: Is this what you are wearing right now?
德比:是的.
Debbie: It sure is.
开萝尔:我唯一的办法是……
Carol: That my only course of action is...
德比和雪莉:不化妆!
Debbie and Shelly: No make up!
开萝尔:是的.你们怎么猜出来的?
Carol: Right. How did you guess?
雪莉:你疯了?
Shelly: Are you nuts?
开萝尔:不,我很现实.我知道我不属于这些人.
Carol: no, I'm realistic. And I know I don't belong with these people.
雪莉:我们都不是.
Shelly: Neither do we.
开萝尔:今天喊到我名字的时候,我将拒绝这个提名.
Carol: And when my name is called today, I'm going to decline the nomination.
德比:你真的疯了.
Debbie: You are nuts.
开萝尔:我了解我自己.
Carol: Nope. I just know what I am.
德比:我们离王位这么近.
Debbie: We were this close to royalty.
雪莉:是的,直到你给她化妆成一个马戏团小丑.
Shelly: Yeah. Till you showed her the make up you got from clown school.
红衣女生:你听到了吗?
Girl in red: Did you here that?
蓝衣女生:开萝尔?西维尔要素面示人.
Girl in blue: Carol Seaver's going for the natural look.
绿衣女生:这太老套了,好像你一点都在乎似的.
Girl in green: It's the old humble bit. Act like you don't care at all.
黄衣女生:一个赢得选票的廉价方式.
Girl in yellow: What a cheap way to get votes.
所有人:嗯.
All: Hmmm.
校长:德维中学的精英们.你们其余人都要向他们学习.你从燃起大火的大楼里救了多少人,伽瑞丝?
Principle: Dewey Highs finest. The rest of you could learn from their example. How many people did you pull from that burning building Gareth?
伽瑞丝:二十四个,先生.
Gareth: Twenty four, sir.
校长:你们听见了吗?看我们返校节王后的候选人们.她们是多么的可爱!
Principle: Did you hear that? Hu? Sir. Turning our attention now to some more fine Hooters, the candidates for homecoming queen. All visions of loveliness and what the hell happened to you?
开萝尔:德维先生,我诚意地请求收回我的提名.
Carol: Mr. Dewitt. I respectfully decline my nomination.
校长:什么?你不可以.
Principle: What? You can't.
女生甲:我也希望收回我的提名.
Girl 1: I respectfully decline my nomination too.
校长:拉拉队长?
Principle: The head cheerleader?
女生乙:我也是.
Girl 2: Me too.
其他女生:我们都是.
Other girls: So do we.
雪莉和德比:我们要,我们要.
Shelly and Debbie: We'll do it. We'll do it.
校长:放开,放开.你们这些女孩子,别抓住我.
Principle: Get away. Get away. You girls will resign over my dead body. Got that? Let go of it.
开萝尔:如果他们不收回对我愚蠢的提名,我今晚就不去参加这个愚蠢的舞会.
Carol: Well if they won't let me decline their stupid nomination, I just won't go to their stupid dance tonight.
麦琪:为什么是愚蠢的?
Maggie: Why is it stupid?
开萝尔:他们都想羞辱我.
Carol: They are trying to rub my nose in it.
麦琪:在哪方面羞辱你?
Maggie: Rub your nose in what?
开萝尔:事实上他们是如此完美.
Carol: The fact that they are so perfect.
麦琪:开萝尔,我听起来,你担心他们比你好.
Maggie: Carol, it sounds to me like you are afraid that they are better than you are.
开萝尔:很明显,你没有听我,和前返校节王后说话真是浪费时间.
Carol: Well obviously you have not heard a word I've said, and it's a waste of time to talk to a former homecoming queen.
麦琪:别用这种口气和我说话,年轻的小姐,如果你想好了,你就别去舞会.
Maggie: Don't take that tone with me young lady, or you'll be grounded and you won't go to that dance.
开萝尔:那正是我想要的,妈妈.
Carol: That's what I want mum. Ground me.
麦琪:绝对不要.现在回到你的房间,别出来.除非是去舞会.还有你,怎么直到现在才来?
Maggie: Absolutely not. Now go to your room and don't come out. Except to go to the dance. And you. You wait till now to come in?
杰森:哦,你说你想处理的.
Jason: Oh, you said you wanted to handle it.
麦琪:你听我的话?
Maggie: And you listen to me?
杰森:带给你们一点小吃.
Jason: Brought you a little snack.
开萝尔:怎么回事,你觉得我还不够胖吗?
Carol: What's the matter, I'm not fat enough for you?
杰森:哦,不.你是……哦,不.你知道我什么意思.这就是你不想穿的返校节礼服?
Jason: Oh no. You are plenty f...Oh no. You know what I mean. Is this the homecoming dress that you are not going to wear?
开萝尔:你们别劝我去参加那种舞会.
Carol: You're not going to get me to go to that dance.
杰森:嘿,你自己拿主意,我尊重你.
Jason: Hey, you make your own decisions. I respect them.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thank you.
杰森:你不再是一个小女孩了.看这张照片.这个丝带是什么?二年级拼写B的奖品.
Jason: Not like you are a little girl anymore. Like in this picture. What was this ribbon? Second grade spelling B.
开萝尔:是,是的,是的.
Carol: Yes, Y E S, yes.
杰森:多可爱啊.和你妈妈一样的幽默感.
Jason: Cute. Same sense of humour as your mother.
开萝尔:她认为我应当有一个愉快的回忆.
Carol: She thinks I should go and have a pleasant memory.
杰森:嘿,那时没有压力.啊.你的快乐营奖章.你还记得吗?
Jason: Hey, no pressure here. Ahhh, your happy camper medal. Do you remember that?
开萝尔:那是我才七岁.
Carol: Barely. I was seven.
杰森:还记得你妈妈和我拉你第一次去快乐营仪式,你又踢又叫的样子吗.
Jason: Remember how your mum and I had to drag you kicking and screaming to your first happy camper meeting. Hu?
开萝尔:爸爸,我最尊敬的爸爸,你是有所指呢,还是只是唠叨而已?
Carol: Dad, with all due respect, do you have a point, or are you just babbling?
杰森:只是唠叨.哦,看,这张你戴着眼镜.那是什么?两年前了.我甚至认不出那个女孩了.
Jason: Just babbling. Oh look, oh there you are with your glasses on. And what was that? Two years ago. I don't even recognize that girl.
开萝尔:那是我.
Carol: It's me.
杰森:我在想那些日子已经过去了,已不再是我所了解的开萝尔?西维尔了.
Jason: I guess the days of overalls and baby fat are gone now. This is not the Carol Seaver I know anymore.
开萝尔:爸爸,那不是唠叨,你是有所指的.
Carol: Dad, that is not babbling, that's a point.
杰森:我只是想在我的记忆长廊中作一次小小的旅行,了解我的小女孩是怎样成长为一个如此漂亮的女人.你知道,事情有时候发生的如此之快,以至于我们忘记察觉别人的变化,包括我们自己.
Jason: Well I just wanted to take a little trip down memory lane, to see how my little girl had grown up into such an incredibly beautiful woman. You know, things happen so fast sometimes that we forget to see the changes in a person. In ourselves.
开萝尔:我更喜欢听你只是唠叨.
Carol: I liked it better when you were just babbling.
杰森:你真像你的妈妈.
Jason: You are just like your mum.
开萝尔:迈克,侮辱我.
Carol: Mike, insult me.
迈克:什么,你不会敲门?什么,你是在猪圈中长大的吗?
Mike: What, don't you knock? What, were you raised in a barn?
开萝尔:那不是侮辱.
Carol: That's not an insult.
迈克:这是什么?
Mike: What is this?
开萝尔:来,像你以往侮辱我那样.
Carol: Come on. I was counting on you treating me like you always have.
迈克:那是怎样的?
Mike: And how's that?
开萝尔:像个渣滓.现在继续吧.讲一个老掉牙的长玩笑.
Carol: Like scum. Now come on. How about a fat joke for old times sake.
迈克:一个长玩笑.好.我要你坐下来,不过……
Mike: A fat joke. Alright uh. Ok uh. Well I'd ask you to sit down, but...
开萝尔:好的.
Carol: Yeah.
迈克:好,加油.你把我的玩笑弄没了,开萝尔.
Mike: Now come on. You're taking all the fun out of this Carol.
开萝尔:好,换个短一点的吧
Carol: Ok, the how about a nerd joke.
迈克:好的,一个短笑话,行.
Mike: Ok. A nerd joke, great.
开萝尔:我不能帮你.
Carol: I won't help you.
迈克:好的,我要你坐下来,但是……哦,不.那是我的玩笑.我没辙了,我没辙了.
Mike: Ok. Well I'd ask you to sit down, but... Oh no. That was my fat joke. I'm loosing it, I'm loosing it. Um,
开萝尔:加油,迈克.你可以做到.我需要一次侮辱.你是我唯一一个不会骗我的人.
Carol: Come on Mike. You can do it. I need one insult. You're the only person I know who won't lie to me.
迈克:我承受不了压力,开萝尔.
Mike: I don't do well under pressure Carol.
开萝尔:我知道,我看过你的成绩单.
Carol: I know. I've seen your grades.
迈克:好,你还想让我侮辱你吗?
Mike: Ok, who's supposed to be doing the insults here?
开萝尔:你这个笨蛋.开始吧!想想.想想胖子,肥猪,人体轮胎.
Carol: You are weenie. Now come on! Think. Think blimps, pigs, wide body tires.
迈克:轮胎?
Mike: Tires?
开萝尔:书呆子,四只眼,卑微,滑稽.
Carol: Brains, four eyes, nerds, geeks.
迈克:好的,好的,你并不卑微,你没有以前胖了.你还要什么?
Mike: Alright, alright, you're not a nerd and you're not fat anymore. What do you want from me?
开萝尔:哦,你下一步要说我是那堆无所事事的人当中的一个.
Carol: Oh, and the next thing you are going to say is that I'm part of the in crowd and the A list and the sociees.
迈克:当然,你是.每个人都知道.
Mike: well of course you are. Everybody knows that.
开萝尔:谢谢,迈克.谢谢你了.
Carol: Oh thanks Mike. Thanks for nothing.
迈克:好了.你知道,你有一张很大的……像你这样的一张脸,你可以……哦,不,忘记了.
Mike: Well alright. You know, you've got one humungous uh...uh... And with a face like yours, you could...uh...Oh no, it's gone.
开萝尔:今年将成为一个马戏团主题.
Carol: It is going to be a circus theme this year.
红衣女生:衣服真漂亮.
Girl in red: Great dress.
开萝尔:你在说我?
Carol: You're talking to me?
红衣女生:是的.
Girl in red: Yeah.
开萝尔:谢谢你们.
Carol: Well thank you.
二人:我太紧张了.
Both together: I'm so nervous.
二人:你紧张吗?
Both together: You're nervous?
开萝尔:你知道什么?哦,詹尼弗,你看起来光彩照人.
Carol: What do you know? Oh Jennifer, you look radiant.
詹尼弗:谢谢你.我得去吐一下.
Jennifer: Thank you. I have to throw up.
开萝尔:她也紧张.
Carol: She's nervous too.
蓝衣女生:我知道你在想什么?
Girl in blue: I know what you are thinking.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
蓝衣女生:你在想我不属于这儿.
Girl in blue: That I don't belong here.
开萝尔:哦,不,不.
Carol: Oh no. No.
蓝衣女生:你是对的.
Girl in blue: Well, you are right.
粉红女生:你们在笑什么?
Girl in pink: What are you smiling at?
开萝尔:我觉得没有人认为他们属于这儿.
Carol: I'm getting the feeling that nobody thinks they belong here.
粉红女生:不是每一个人都和你一样,但是你也不必羞辱我们.
Girl in pink: Not everybody is in your league, but you don't have to rub our noses in it.
开萝尔:和我不一样?
Carol: Not in my league?
粉红女生:哦,你属于所有俱乐部.你成绩好,头发也好.
Girl in pink: Oh come on. You are in all the clubs. You got great grades, great hair.
红衣女生:就是这!
Girl in red: This is it!
詹尼弗:哦,不.
Jennifer: Oh no. Not again.
小伙:大家准备好.
Guy: Get ready people.
校长:请候选人上场.
Principle: I present the homecoming court.
粉红女生:我们不能没有詹尼弗.
Girl in pink: We can't leave without Jennifer.
红衣女生:哦,是的,我们可以.
Girl in red: Oh yes, we can.
校长:你们需要电报催促的吗? 动起来,动起来,动起来!
Principle: Do you people need a telegram? Let's move it, move it, move it!
开萝尔男伴:我们最好现在就走.
Carol's man: We're supposed to go now.
开萝尔:等一会.
Carol: In a minute.
开萝尔男伴:等一会!
Carol's man: In a minute!
开萝尔:那真的是我.
Carol: It's really me.
开萝尔男伴:嗯.你是不是很紧张?
Carol's man: Uh hu. Are you having a nervous breakdown or something?
开萝尔:不是.我已经紧张过了,我们走吧.
Carol: Nope. I already had it. Let's go.
杰森:她来这儿了.
Jason: Here she is.
开萝尔:你们好.
Carol: Hello.
麦琪:你好,宝贝.舞会怎么样?
Maggie: Hi honey. How was the dance?
开萝尔:太棒了.
Carol: Wonderful.
杰森:你获胜了吗?你成了新的了吗?你玩得开心吗?
Jason: Well, did you win the, uh? Are you the new, uh? You had a good time?
开萝尔:非常好.
Carol: Perfect.
麦琪:返校节场地如何?
Maggie: And the homecoming court was?
开萝尔:非常华丽.
Carol: Magnificent.
麦琪:哦,开萝尔,你呢?
Maggie: Oh Carol, did you?
开萝尔:不,何瑟?麦克唐纳德布置的.不过我们得到了玫瑰,和一个大的金项链.
Carol: No. Heather McDonald did. But we all got roses and a big gold bracelet.
杰森:哦,那太棒了.
Jason: Oh, that's beautiful.
麦琪:哦,那太棒了.
Maggie: Oh, that's wonderful.
开萝尔:妈妈,你是对的.那将是一段美好的回忆.晚安.
Carol: And mum, you were right. It will be a wonderful memory. Night.
麦琪:晚安.
Maggie: Night.
迈克:哦,开萝尔.我需要你.好了,来这儿,你准备好了吗?他们做了一个三层高的王座给你了吗?
Mike: Oh, Carol, I need you. Alright. Here, are you ready for this? Here it comes. So, like, did they make a triple sized throne for you?
开萝尔:谢谢你,迈克.那很有趣.
迈克:我知道,我刚刚丢了它.
00:23:29,800
Carol: Thank you Mike. That was very sweet. Mike: I knew it. I am losing it.